Guide to the American Federation of Teachers Local 200 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- American Federation of Teachers Local 200 records, 1964-1982; 1909-005; 4.03 cubic feet 4 boxes 1 vertical file
  - PUBLICATIONS, 1966-1980; SERIES VI (Box-folder 3/2-3/27)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Organizing: Elections Procedures, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 3/24)
    - News Clipping: The Seattle Weekly: "A masquerade of militarism" by David Brewster, 1976 (Box-folder 3/25)
    - Original Drawings by K. Cragg and Others for Seattle Federation of Teachers Publications, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 3/26)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publication Drafts, News Clippings, Photographs, and Illustrations, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 3/27)
  - CONTRACT ENFORCEMENT, 1968-1979; SERIES VII (Box-folder 3/28-4/87)
    - Lawsuit: Angevine, et al., v. Seattle School District: King County Superior Court Case No. 795060, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 3/28)
    - Legal File: Seattle Federation of Teachers: Attorney Peter D. Francis, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 3/29)
    - Legal File: Seattle Federation of Teachers: Invoices from the Law Offices of MacDonald, Hoague & Bayless, 1975 (Box-folder 3/30)
    - Legal File: Seattle Federation of Teachers: Invoices from the Law Offices of MacDonald, Hoague & Bayless, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 3/31)
    - Legal and Insurance Documents: Monumental Life Insurance Company: Roman C. Taruc and Pilar Ocampo Taruc, 1976 (Box-folder 3/32)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Executive Board Telephone Tree, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3/33)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Program of Action, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 3/34)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Program of Action, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 3/35)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Program of Action, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 3/36)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Program of Action, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 3/37)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Program of Action, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 3/38)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Program of Action, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 3/39)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Drafts of Publications and Illustrations, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 3/40)
    - Unemployment Claims, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 3/41)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Contract Non-Renewal Hearings, 1975 (Box-folder 3/42)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Contract Non-Renewal Hearings, 1976 (Box-folder 3/43)
    - Grievance: Garfield High School, 1973 (Box-folder 3/44)
    - Grievance: Whitman Junior High School, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 3/45)
    - Contract: Provisional Elementary School Part-Time Contract, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 3/46)
    - Correspondence from Members, 1972 (Box-folder 3/47)
    - Arbitration: Garfield High School, 1971 (Box-folder 3/48)
    - Grievance: Ryther Child Center, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 3/49)
    - Loss of Sick Days: Seattle Public Schools, 1976 (Box-folder 3/50)
    - Grievance: Queen Anne High School, 1975 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Grievance: Lincoln High/Monroe Junior High, 1975 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - Lawsuit: Seattle School District: Right to Remain Employed after age 65, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Contract/Permanent Placement Issue: Seattle School District, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Teacher Assistant Position: Hamilton Middle School, 1968 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Arbitration: Seattle School District, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Arbitration: Seattle School District, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Grievance: Asa Mercer Middle School, 1974 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Performance Review: NOVA High School, 1976 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Non-Renewal of Contract: Lawsuit: Seattle Public Schools, 1975 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Resignation: Seattle Public Schools, 1974 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Grievance: Seward Elementary, 1975 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Grievance: Eckstein Middle School, 1972 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Greivance: Mercer Junior High School, 1974 (Box-folder 4/14)
    - Grievance: Madison Junior High School, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Arbitration: Seattle Public Schools, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 4/16)
    - Grievance: Rainier Beach High School, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 4/17)
    - Grievance: Sealth High School, 1975 (Box-folder 4/18)
    - ACTION/Peace Corps Credit: Seattle Public Schools, 1975 (Box-folder 4/19)
    - Seniority and Salary Credit: Seattle Public Schools, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 4/20)
    - Retirement Benefits: Wilson Junior High School, 1975 (Box-folder 4/21)
    - Work Issue: Cooper Elementary School, circa 1970-circa 1976 (Box-folder 4/22)
    - Field Notes: Former Teacher and Seattle Federation of Teachers Member, 1972 (Box-folder 4/23)
    - Nonrenewal of Contract: Seattle Public Schools, 1975 (Box-folder 4/24)
    - Grievance: Nathan Hale High School, 1975 (Box-folder 4/25)
    - Grievance: Wilson Middle School, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 4/26)
    - Insurance Coverage Issue: Seattle School District, 1972 (Box-folder 4/27)
    - Teacher Position Issue: Indian Heritage High School/Madrona Middle School, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 4/28)
    - Grievance: Sharples Junior High School, 1975 (Box-folder 4/29)
    - Grievance: Leschi Middle School, 1975 (Box-folder 4/30)
    - Leave Issue: Seattle Public Schools, 1972 (Box-folder 4/31)
    - Grievance: Madrona Middle School, 1972 (Box-folder 4/32)
    - Grievance: Madrona Middle School, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4/33)
    - Grievance: Queen Anne High School, 1975 (Box-folder 4/34)
    - Work Issue, 1975 (Box-folder 4/35)
    - Probation and Resignation: Franklin High School, 1976 (Box-folder 4/36)
    - Resignation: Cultural Pluralism Project, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 4/37)
    - Substitute Teacher Evaluation: Madrona Middle School, 1976 (Box-folder 4/38)
    - Grievance: Franklin High School, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 4/39)
    - Grievance: Wilson Middle School, 1973 (Box-folder 4/40)
    - Grievance: Wilson Middle School, 1973 (Box-folder 4/41)
    - Grievance: Asa Mercer Middle School, 1974 (Box-folder 4/42)
    - Work Issues: Jane Addams Middle School, circa 1970-circa 1976 (Box-folder 4/43)
    - Teacher Surplussing: Oak Lake Elementary School, 1973 (Box-folder 4/44)
    - Nonrenewal of Contract Hearing Findings: Seattle School District No. 1, 1974 (Box-folder 4/45)
    - Work Issue: Ryther Child Center, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4/46)
    - Work Issue: Wilson Middle School, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4/47)
    - Grievance: Monroe Middle School, 1973 (Box-folder 4/48)
    - Pay Issue: Hamilton Middle School, 1972 (Box-folder 4/49)
    - Pay Issue: Hamilton Middle School, 1973 (Box-folder 4/50)
    - Grievance: Kimball Elementary School, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 4/51)
    - Grievance: Nathan Hale High School, 1974 (Box-folder 4/52)
    - Grievance: Colman School, 1972 (Box-folder 4/53)
    - Contract Issue: Lincoln High School, 1972 (Box-folder 4/54)
    - Grievance: Hamilton Middle School, 1973 (Box-folder 4/55)
    - Grievance: Jefferson School, 1972 (Box-folder 4/56)
    - Grievance: Garfield High School, 1975 (Box-folder 4/57)
    - Pay Issue: Central Area Schools, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 4/58)
    - Work Issue: Daniel Bagley Elementary School, 1975 (Box-folder 4/59)
    - Sex Discrimination: Washington Teachers Credit Union Credit Committee, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 4/60)
    - Teacher Placement Issue: Garfield High School, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 4/61)
    - Work Issue: Nathan Hale High School, 1972 (Box-folder 4/62)
    - Grievance: Madrona, 1971 (Box-folder 4/63)
    - Grievance: Maple Leaf, 1973 (Box-folder 4/64)
    - Transfer Issue, circa 1970-circa 1976 (Box-folder 4/65)
    - Grievance: Nova, 1973 (Box-folder 4/66)
    - Grievance: Seattle Public Schools: Librarian Per Diem Days, 1975 (Box-folder 4/67)
    - Personnel File Inquiry, circa 1970-circa 1976 (Box-folder 4/68)
    - Reduction in Home Economics Staff: Chief Sealth High School, 1974 (Box-folder 4/69)
    - Work Issue, 1972 (Box-folder 4/70)
    - Work Issue: Thomson Junior High School, 1976 (Box-folder 4/71)
    - Grievance: Rainier Beach High School, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 4/72)
    - Contract Issue, 1975 (Box-folder 4/73)
    - Death of Angeles (Lita) Taruc: Teacher at Sanislo Elementary School, 1976 (Box-folder 4/74)
    - Teacher Corps: Madrona, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 4/75)
    - Grievance: Monroe Junior High School, 1973 (Box-folder 4/76)
    - Correspondence: Affirmative Action, 1976 (Box-folder 4/77)
    - Work Issue: Madison Junior High School, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 4/78)
    - Grievance: Sharples Junior High School, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4/79)
    - Grievance: Indian Heritage High School/Rainier Beach High School, 1975 (Box-folder 4/80)
    - Contract Issue: Seattle Public Schools, 1976 (Box-folder 4/81)
    - Grievance: Roosevelt High School, circa 1970-circa 1976 (Box-folder 4/82)
    - Grievance: Mercer Junior High School, 1973 (Box-folder 4/83)
    - Brief to the Seattle School Board from Staff: Wilson Middle School: Special Education, 1974 (Box-folder 4/84)
    - Correspondence: Gaye Wood and Attorney C. Dean Little, 1974 (Box-folder 4/85)
    - Correspondence: Norma Zimmerman, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 4/86)
    - Field Notes: Work Issues, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 4/87)
  - CONVENTIONS, 1974-1979; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 4/88-4/89)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Convention: Edgewater Hotel, Seattle, 1979 (Box-folder 4/88)
    - Washington State Federation of Teachers Conventions, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 4/89)
  - SUBJECT FILES, 1964-1973; SERIES IX (Box-folder 4/90-4/94)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 4/90)
    - Teacher Salaries, 1964-1972 (Box-folder 4/91)
    - Political Committees, 1976 (Box-folder 4/92)
    - Sally Pangborn, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 4/93)
    - Sally Pangborn, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 4/94)
  - SCHOOL FILES, 1968-1976; SERIES X (Box-folder 4/95-4/114)
    - Ballard High School, 1976 (Box-folder 4/95)
    - Cleveland High School, 1972 (Box-folder 4/96)
    - Garfield High School A, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 4/97)
    - Nathan Hale High School, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 4/98)
    - Ingraham High School, 1973 (Box-folder 4/99)
    - Maps: Seattle Public Schools: Geographical Divisions for Organization, circa 1970-circa 1976 (Box-folder 4/100)
    - Thomson Junior High School, 1973 (Box-folder 4/101)
    - Whitman Middle School, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 4/102)
    - Hamilton Middle School, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 4/103)
    - Madrona Middle School, circa 1970-circa 1976 (Box-folder 4/104)
    - Meany Middle School, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 4/105)
    - Wilson Junior High School, 1969 (Box-folder 4/106)
    - Elementary Schools, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 4/107)
    - Madison Middle School, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 4/108)
    - Asa Mercer Junior High School, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 4/109)
    - Chief Sealth High School, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4/110)
    - Roosevelt High School, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 4/111)
    - Lincoln High School, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 4/112)
    - Queen Anne High School, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 4/113)
    - Rainier Beach High School, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 4/114)
  - COMMITTEES AND SUBGROUPS, 1970-1982; SERIES XI (Box-folder 4/115-4/121)
    - Membership List: Committee on Political Education, 1982 (Box-folder 4/115)
    - QuEST Teacher-to-Teacher Conference: Quality Educational Standards in Teaching, 1974 (Box-folder 4/116)
    - Outreach Correspondence: QuEST Conference, 1974 (Box-folder 4/117)
    - Planning and Draft Documents: QuEST Conference, 1974 (Box-folder 4/118)
    - Correspondence, Research, Grants, Leaflets: QuEST Conference, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 4/119)
    - Photographs: QuEST Conference, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 4/120)
    - Liaison Committee, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 4/121)
- American Federation of Teachers Local 200 records, 1963-1979; 1909-006; 2 cubic feet 2 boxes
  Correspondence, minutes, press releases, strike files and related records; 1963-1979.
  Accession includes files from the 1970s, when classroom discipline, race relations, and busing were important concerns. The Subject Series in Box 2 include records of the G. Sally Pangborn lawsuit regarding dismissal of a popular teacher.
  Seattle Federation of Teachers, January 27, 1983
  - American Federation of Teachers Local 200, 1963-1979; RECORD GROUP 1 (Box-folder 1/1-2/36)
    - MEMBERSHIP, 1969-1976; SERIES I (Box-folder 1/1-1/3)
      - Seattle Teachers Association: Membership and Agency Shop Controversy, 1976 (Box-folder 1/1)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Membership, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 1/2)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Building Representative Telephone Tree, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - CORRESPONDENCE, 1966-1979; SERIES II (Box-folder 1/4-1/20)
      - Kenneth R. Warren, President, Seattle Federation of Teachers: Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 1/4)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: General Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 1/5)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Correspondence Regarding Contracts, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 1/6)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Letters to the Editors of Various Newspapers, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 1/7)
      - Stanton Bloom, Director, Seattle Federation of Teachers: Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 1/8)
      - Stanton Bloom, Director, Seattle Federation of Teachers: Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 1/9)
      - Marjorie Stern, Field Representative, Seattle Federation of Teachers: Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 1/10)
      - Virgil Holland, President, Seattle Federation of Teachers: Incoming Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 1/11)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Membership Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 1/12)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Membership Correspondence, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 1/13)
      - Virgil Holland, President, Seattle Federation of Teachers: Outgoing Correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 1/14)
      - Don Burns, President, Seattle Federation of Teachers: Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 1/15)
      - John E. Dunn, President, Seattle Federation of Teachers: Correspondence, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 1/16)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Treasurer Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 1/17)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Correspondence with the Seattle Teachers Association, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 1/18)
      - Template: Visitation Authorization Letter from Kenneth R. Warren, President, Seattle Federation of Teachers, circa 1970-circa 1971 (Box-folder 1/19)
      - Correspondence: Washington State Federation of Teachers and Seattle Federation of Teachers Liaison Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - MINUTES, 1969-1972; SERIES III (Box-folder 1/21-1/22)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 1/21)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1970-1979; SERIES IV (Box-folder 1/23-1/28)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Financial Statements, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 1/23)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Local 609 Strike Fund, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 1/24)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Financial Statements, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 1/25)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Payroll Deductions, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 1/26)
      - Invoices from the American Federation of Teachers to the Seattle Federation of Teachers, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 1/27)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: American Federation of Teachers Aid Program, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 1/28)
    - GRANT APPLICATIONS, 1969-1976; SERIES V (Box-folder 1/29-1/30)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers Grant Applications, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 1/29)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers Application for Grant from the American Federation of Teachers, 1976 (Box-folder 1/30)
    - PRESS RELEASES, 1969-1973; SERIES VI (Box-folder 1/31-1/32)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Press Releases, 1971 (Box-folder 1/31)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Press Releases, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 1/32)
    - NEWSLETTERS AND MAILINGS, 1969-1977; SERIES VII (Box-folder 1/33-1/37)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers Contract Negotiations and Agency Shop Controversy, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 1/33)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Building Representatives Bulletins and Related Literature, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 1/34)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Building Representatives Bulletins and Related Literature, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 1/35)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Member and Executive Board Mailings and Meeting Agendas, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 1/36)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers Membership Drive, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 1/37)
    - PETITIONS, 1972-1976; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 1/38-1/42)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Involuntary Transfer Petition, 1974 (Box-folder 1/38)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Petition Against an Agency Shop, 1976 (Box-folder 1/39)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Petition Against an Agency Shop, 1975 (Box-folder 1/40)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Petition Against an Agency Shop, 1976 (Box-folder 1/41)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Dues Deduction Petitions, 1972 (Box-folder 1/42)
    - STRIKES, 1971-1976; SERIES IX (Box-folder 1/43-1/47)
      - Strikes: Press, Bulletins, and Correspondence with Other Unions, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 1/43)
      - Strike Planning and Inter-Organization Cooperation Between the Seattle Teachers Association and Seattle Federation of Teachers, 1974 (Box-folder 1/44)
      - Operating Engineers Strike, 1975 (Box-folder 1/45)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Strike Authorization and Bulletins, 1976 (Box-folder 1/46)
      - Memorandum of Understanding: Strike Reprisals, 1975 (Box-folder 1/47)
    - SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, 1971-1973; SERIES X (Box-folder 1/48-1/49)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: President's Statements, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 1/48)
      - Statement of Ross K. Rieder, President, Washington State Federation of Teachers to Joint Committee on Education Meeting: Teacher Tenure, 1971 (Box-folder 1/49)
    - ELECTIONS, 1971; SERIES XI (Box-folder 1/50)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Elections, 1971 (Box-folder 1/50)
    - CLIPPINGS, 1976; SERIES XII (Box-folder 1/51)
      - News Clippings, 1976 (Box-folder 1/51)
    - GRIEVANCE FILES, 1963-1976; SERIES XIII (Box-folder 2/1-2/18)
      - Grievance: Worth McClure Junior High School, 1963-1971 (Box-folder 2/1)
      - Grievance: Lincoln High School, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Grievance: Garfield High School, 1971 (Box-folder 2/3)
      - Grievance: Alternative School, 1971 (Box-folder 2/4)
      - Grievance: Seattle Public School Board, 1971 (Box-folder 2/5)
      - Lawsuit and Liability Insurance Issue: Whitman, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 2/6)
      - Grievance: CAMPI Preschool, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 2/7)
      - Grievance: Seattle Public Schools, 1976 (Box-folder 2/8)
      - Work Issue, 1976 (Box-folder 2/9)
      - Grievance: Asa Mercer Middle School, 1976 (Box-folder 2/10)
      - Grievance: Seattle Public Schools, 1976 (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Arbitration: Seattle Public Schools, 1976 (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Grievance: Lincoln High School Special Education Department, 1976 (Box-folder 2/13)
      - Work Injuries: Indian Heritage School, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 2/14)
      - Power of Attorney to Seattle Federation of Teachers, 1976 (Box-folder 2/15)
      - Grievance: Jane Addams Junior High School, 1976 (Box-folder 2/16)
      - Grievance: West Woodland Elementary, 1976 (Box-folder 2/17)
      - Work Issue: Ingraham High School, circa 1970-circa 1976 (Box-folder 2/18)
    - SUBJECT FILES, 1969-1977; SERIES XIV (Box-folder 2/19-2/36)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers Pre-Authorized Check Plan, 1975 (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Alternative Dues Deduction Procedures, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 2/20)
      - Paraprofessionals: Contact Negotiations and Enforcement, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 2/21)
      - Sally Pangborn: Unjust Firing, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Organizing Materials and Literature, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 2/23)
      - Organizing Correspondence and Reports, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 2/24)
      - Member Death: William V. Bernnard: Homicide News Clippings and Life Insurance Documents, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 2/25)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Cartoons and Artwork, circa 1970-circa 1976 (Box-folder 2/26)
      - Summer School, 1972 (Box-folder 2/27)
      - Voucher Plan, 1971 (Box-folder 2/28)
      - Proposal for a Woman Coordinator of Girls' Physical Education Program: Seattle School Board, 1972 (Box-folder 2/29)
      - Grievance Handling, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 2/30)
      - Levy, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 2/31)
      - Teacher Problem Clinic, circa 1970-circa 1976 (Box-folder 2/32)
      - Performance Contracting, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 2/33)
      - Mergers, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 2/34)
      - Magnet Program Issue: Phyllis King, 1977 (Box-folder 2/35)
      - Washington State Labor Council, 1970 (Box-folder 2/36)
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF TEACHERS LOCAL 200: EXECUTIVE BOARD, 1969-1972; RECORD GROUP 2 (Box-folder 2/37-2/39)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 2/37)
    - Minutes, Newsletters, and Financial Statements (1 of 2), 1969-1972 (Box-folder 2/38)
    - Minutes, Newsletters, and Financial Statements (2 of 2), 1969-1972 (Box-folder 2/39)
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF TEACHERS LOCAL 200: SEATTLE MINORITY TEACHERS ASSOCIATION, 1976; RECORD GROUP 3 (Box-folder 2/40)
    - Seattle Minority Teachers Association, 1976 (Box-folder 2/40)